{
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who is the protagonist of 'The Legend of Zelda'?",
        "answers": [
          "Link",
          "Zelda",
          "Ganon",
          "Navi"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Link"
      },
      {
        "question": "In which game do you explore the island of 'Myst'?",
        "answers": [
          "Myst",
          "Riven",
          "The Witness",
          "Journey"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Myst"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the main objective in 'Uncharted: Drake's Fortune'?",
        "answers": [
          "Find a lost treasure",
          "Save a princess",
          "Escape from a maze",
          "Solve a mystery"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Find a lost treasure"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which game features a character named 'Lara Croft'?",
        "answers": [
          "Tomb Raider",
          "Assassin's Creed",
          "Prince of Persia",
          "God of War"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Tomb Raider"
      },
      {
        "question": "In which adventure game is the world of 'Hyrule' found?",
        "answers": [
          "The Legend of Zelda",
          "Final Fantasy",
          "Dark Souls",
          "Skyrim"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "The Legend of Zelda"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the protagonist in 'The Last Guardian'?",
        "answers": [
          "Trico",
          "Ico",
          "Shadows of the Colossus",
          "Yorda"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Trico"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which adventure game focuses on exploring an open world and solving puzzles?",
        "answers": [
          "The Witness",
          "Firewatch",
          "Life is Strange",
          "Grim Fandango"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "The Witness"
      },
      {
        "question": "In which game do you control a young girl named 'Max Caulfield'?",
        "answers": [
          "Life is Strange",
          "The Walking Dead",
          "Heavy Rain",
          "Beyond: Two Souls"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Life is Strange"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the main objective in 'Grim Fandango'?",
        "answers": [
          "Escape from the underworld",
          "Solve a mystery",
          "Find a treasure",
          "Save a friend"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Escape from the underworld"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which adventure game takes place in a fantasy world filled with magical creatures?",
        "answers": [
          "Ni no Kuni",
          "Final Fantasy",
          "Dark Souls",
          "The Witcher"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Ni no Kuni"
      }
    ]
  }